

ADAM MCGURK

eldermcgurk@gmail.com | (408) 693-5992

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Passionate Lead Developer with a four year background in building web and mobile applications. Experienced with building and maintaining multiple high volume applications at the same time. Skilled in leading a highly efficient product development team while maintaining excellent code quality and user satisfaction.

SKILLS

- HTML5/CSS3/JS&TypeScript
- React Native
- PHP/Node.JS

- MySQL/MariaDB
- AWS/Google Cloud Platform

WORK HISTORY

Lead Developer | Shine Solar - Bentonville, AR

06/2018 - CURRENT

- Orchestrated efficient large-scale software deployments, including testing features and correcting code.
- · Built the company's customer facing mobile application
- Built the company's internal marketing and sales system (CRM)
- Led a team of six developers as we maintained software for those systems on the web, mobile, and desktop platforms.
- Maintained applications and application servers that saw traffic in the millions per month

Lead Web Developer | Emperium - Rexburg, ID

06/2017 - 06/2018

- Developed, coded and updated Marketing and Sales sites for clients such as Dean Graziosi and Paradigm Direct.
- Maintained the company's application servers in Amazon Web Servers
- Built optimized landing pages in HTML and CSS, including API integration and cross-browser compatibility, to support marketing.
- · Led the engineering vision as the startup grew

Chief Engineer | BYU-Idaho - Rexburg, ID

08/2016 - 04/2018

- Led a team of network and systems engineers as we supported the radio station's technologies
- Built internal web applications to monitor uptime and increase efficiency
- Configured and maintained Cisco networking equipment and Windows Server machines
- Maintained remote transmitter systems in more than ten different locations

EDUCATION

BYU Idaho, Rexburg, Idaho

EXPECTED IN 04/2020

Bachelor of Science: Computer Information Technology